{
    "id": "126cf2012a3347ec960fa8c7e5758b72",
    "title": "Prepositions Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It would be a good idea to compare this year’s accounts ……………………………. last year’s.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "52834119efb14ddfa38fc027b4d36960"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. friends like you, who needs enemies?",
            "description": "With can introduce the reason for a situation.",
            "answers": [
                "With",
                "For",
                "From"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4ab6910ceaad438392c4f0d4521ea3da"
        },
        {
            "question": "Is he worth talking ………………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5779ab8a780047aa912f8bb780c7ec6d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you talking ……………………… such a loud voice?",
            "description": "We say in a …. voice.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "950d99d4c2ca4aa595f7b1889cfba80b"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you go ………………………. car, you will reach there in 2 hours.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "by",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6cb787fc38484b91ae2bbc32d7ee5daf"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please write …………………….. ink.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "in",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8b76da2662c041cc9c9dba0f5244b846"
        },
        {
            "question": "I want to buy a computer ……………………….. a huge memory.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bb89e5dea72444a5b323f81769e3fd01"
        },
        {
            "question": "Catholics are supposed to go to church ……………………….. Sundays.",
            "description": "We use on before names of days.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f9398939cea94e86b01be990f7786c45"
        },
        {
            "question": "I won’t take a penny …………………………. him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "from",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b95cdb2dab8545018b4fd854c6da7181"
        },
        {
            "question": "Take that dirty hand ………………………… me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "off",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "35b84ca8566549569c4cf844f7d18fd3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He took some money …………………….. his wallet.",
            "description": "Either from or out of is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "out of",
                "from",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "022dab2c216f4a8baf10494efe017750"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have never had any interest ………………………. politics.",
            "description": "We say interest in.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4857505ebb0f4b9db185e9a705cffa04"
        }
    ]
}